Good afternoon, sir.
Yes, I'm here now.
Ta-da!
Lions, which means we're here at the Bernadome!
Yay, yay!
Kuromi and I came here today to watch a game of Lotte of the Western Squad.
Today, I'm going to show you how to enjoy watching a baseball game at the Verna Dome.
Today, Kuromi and I are going to introduce you how to enjoy watching baseball games at the Verna Dome.
Enjoy it!
Shall we go?
Let's go!
There are many photo spots in this Bernadome.
Let's take lots of pictures!
I feel like I'm in a private place.
Be careful.
I hope we can buy some goods.
I'd like to buy some.
I don't have any Lions merchandise.
Which ones do you have the most of?
I don't have much.
But I have a lot of Yakult stuff.
It's really easy to get to.
And it's artificial.
Yes, that's true.
It's Samurai Japan Day today, isn't it?So today is Samurai Japan Day!
Maybe that's why so many people are wearing Japan iniiforms.
I should have brought my own.
I wasn't thinking.
You had it.
When Chromin and I went to see the WBC, he gave it to me.
Thank you.
We didn't have to wait in line.
That's great.
This is Genda.
Thank you very much.
Samurai Japan Day is the day we got ours.
Lions Store
I want to go to Lions Flux!
I'm going to buy some goods!
First sale merchandise!
Here we are.
What do you want to buy?
What am I gonna buy?
I'm gonna buy some matching stuff.
I'll buy some matching stuff.
Uniforms.
Uniforms for Ringo.
What kind of uniforms do you like?
This is this year's uniform.This is this year's uniform
This is normal
I think I'll buy a normal one.
I'll buy this one.
This yellow uniform...
Thank you very much.
This is Seibu Railway's La View.
Seibu Railway's La View express
Seibu Railway's La View
This is the color of the yellow uniform.
I think yellow is rare for Seibu.
It's true that I don't have a yellow image.
I don't think so.
Shall I get the newest one?
Shall I get the newest one or this one?
It says "We are one" on it.
Don't you want the number?
Nash.
What about the one with Kaze Kichan on it?
Yes?
I'll take the normal one.
They're the same.
It's hot out, so a fan would be nice.
A hanging fan.Neck fan
I see you have a cap.
Any other suggestions?
Do you use flags?
Flags.
I'll get the blacks to buy flags.
I brought my own today.
You brought your own?
The one I always use.
Here it is.
There's so many.
I'm choosing.
I have this one.
That's a good one.
This mark.
I'd like to buy the skin of
It's nice.
It's just renewed.
I just saw that it was recently renewed.
I saw a lot of them.
There were a lot of them.
Oh, man!
So many kinds!There are so many different kinds.
I'm thinking of buying a player's towel.
What do you have?
I want one.
This one.
Genda's towel.
I bought it.
This bag.
It's the first time I've had it. Lions.
Shall I change now?
Shall I change?
I'd like to change into this uniform.
I'll go change.
And now, let's open the door to the Black Folks in their uniforms.
I'll open the door.
Sparkle.
Starting today...
I'm a fan of voice actors.
It looks great on you.
Thank you very much.
Since today, I'm a Lions fan.
I'll let you join us.
I'm a Lions fan today.
I look forward to working with you.Pleased to meet you.
Now that you're in your black civilian uni, let's take a picture.
I'd like to take your picture.
I'm used to taking pictures.
Thank you.
You're so cute.
It looks really good on you.
You look better than I do.
Stop it.
I'd like to do this for a minute. I don't see anyone here.
I didn't write anything down.
Thank you. That's nice.
I'm going to go on a little tour now.
Let's go around.
There's a mist.
Let's all go at once.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Mist is cool.
This is so cool. This is great.
This is a good spot for pictures, too. There's no one here.
Oh, my God.
Wait, it's really good.
Oh, my God.Really?
It's so good!
Yeah, thanks!
Wait, the sun is so good!
Hasaki, we've been coordinating so far.
Oh, that's what I'm talking about!
Cheese!
Yes, cheese!
Wow, it looks great!
Thank you!
And there's the director's big
model
A model of the uniform.
Oh, this is good!
I'm the director.
I wanted to capture it on camera.
Certainly.
Natsumi's
Ta-da!
It's so big!
Can you tell how big it is?
Wow!
It's so big!
It's amazing!Wow!
Wow!
Director's spot
Director's spot. Take your picture here, guys.
Shall we go up to the seats?
Yes, let's go to the first floor.
Let's go.
It's uphill.
I'm a little out of breath.
There's a cooler breeze.
There's a cool breeze.
Oh, there's a lot of dolmets.
Tonkatsu (pork cutlet), too. Great!
There's teppanyaki, too.
Looks so delicious!
Great, it was a good workout!
Good exercise. Positive.
My feet are cramping up.
Wow!
Wait, isn't it gorgeous?
Oh, my God, we're almost there.
We're here!
Oh, man!
Oh, man!Oh no!
What's the view of the ballpark?
Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da.
Wow, that's amazing.
Isn't that right under the bleachers?
Oh, yeah.
That's great.
I'd like to go to dinner now.
I'm off.
Oh, there's a delivery for you.
It's a lunch box produced by a player.
Wow, that's great.
One bento for Mr. Kaneko, then.
Thank you.
The starting lineup has been announced.
Genda will start at shortstop.
That's right, number two.
Makino's playing first base today.
And Peiton returns to left.
The catcher is Ogawa.
The other player is Yamaguchi at first base!
He's hit in about 5 straight games.
That's the only thing we have to watch out for.
Block swinging.
I got it just now.I just got it.
Crack.
Everyone's shaking their hands.
It's like giving a towel to a skin man.
Yeah, it's true, they are shaking it.
I can't believe Fresh Kuromi is on the same team.
We're on the same team.
This is the first time I've filmed on YouTube since I've been able to cheer for a baseball team!
So I'm sure you can hear me cheering really loudly today.
Lotte is probably the loudest team in the 12th grade
I think Lotte is a cool team with their cheering songs and so on.
Towel Towel
Go for it, Mr. Gender!
I bought this towel today.
I contacted Mr. Misa and asked him if I could buy a towel for Gender.
That's great of you!
I told him that I was going to see him today, and he said he'd be there to cheer me on.
Oh, really?
Yes, I'll buy one today.
I'd like to introduce the bento I bought today.
First of all...
This is Kaneko's cat's Western-style bento.
How cute!He's so cute!
Here it is, with Kaneko's card.
This is No. 7, too.
Number 7.
Wow, it looks so delicious!
Ta-da!
There's even a waffle in it!
Looks delicious!
I'm off!
And the black meat?
I'm Tatsuya Imai, and I'm Tatsuya Imai's exquisite shrimp cutlet worgar.
Oh, nice!
This one also comes with Imai's card!
With a card.
I'm so happy!
Ta-da!
Wow, gorgeous!
Wow!
It's huge!
It's a big one!
It's as big as a black man's face.
Saki's face.
It's true!
I'd like to eat it while looking at it.
I'd like to eat it slowly, but...But... you know, I'd like to take my time, but...
But I'm worried about the game.
Oh, I see.
I hope you don't get shot.
Hoping.
Wow.
Ooh.
Ghetto Ghetto
Wow.
Yay!
Lovely!
Genta can't get enough of it!
I can't get enough of Genta!
I can't get enough of Genta
Castle while going down
He's so cool!
Oh, here comes Kuriyama!
Ah!
Mr. Kuriyama
Kuriyama is cool!
He's so cool!
He's cool!
Oh, wow!
It's in, it's in!
Oh!Aww.
Yay!
I'm in!
Wait, that's so cool.
I'm so glad I got to see it.
I'm so happy.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's fresh and new.
It's a great trend, isn't it?
You know, I'm going to be tweeting on that screen.
When I graduate.
I'm going to make a Twitter account.
I want to tweet and be on there.
That's my dream.
My account name is
I love Lions!
It's like a Lions fan's Twitter account!
I don't want to be too much of a fore-baller
Oh, there it is!
My back hurts.
I just got a thump on my back.
Oh, wow.
Goodies, goodies, goodies.
Nice.nice
Nice.
Niceable long.
As expected!
That's what I'm talking about.
Too cool!
Every play you see is cool.
The manager is also a Genda-san fan.
I'm so happy. Cheering together.
Only his voice is in the picture.
Tonosaki Shooter
Do you know it? Tell Kuromi.
Tonosaxi Shooter
Tonosaki Shooter
He says he and Kuromi are going to practice Tonosaki's cheering song.
Ouch!
Stop it, really.
The manager is out of control.
It's funny.
I'm glad the manager likes baseball.
It's Hirasawa-san!
Oh no, I'm going to hit it.
Taiga-san is scary.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ahhhh, I did it.
At the very least, at the very least.
I got it under control, under control, somehow.
The manager bought me ice cream.
Yes, I got it. Thank you very much.
I don't spend much.
The ice cream from the manager...
Can I have you come in more and more from now on?
Yes.
The manager bought some ice cream.
Thank you very much.
It's a helmet!
It's a helmet.
You see?
Ice cream in the helmet!
It's got ice cream in it.
Hey, Lions.
Over here, Lotte.
Lotte.
Shiori bought it for me because she likes Rakuten!
Thank you!
Let's give it to Shiori this time.
I see...
Just this.Just this one.
Let's just eat what's inside and pass it on.
Lotte.
Wow!
Wow.
Oh! It's down, it's down.
Two bases.
Two bases for Onozaki.
He's going to hit it.
That's scary. We're still down by one.
Pitcher change.
You're kidding?
No way!
Shunsuke Sato is the same age as you and left-handed.
The same age as Sasaki?
Yes, the same age as me.
Really?
Yes, so I'm rooting for him.
That's great.
Nice.
Well done, sir.
Good job, sir.
Now, roll it up.roll-up function
Oh, no.
Is it in?
It's in.
Two rounds.
I didn't see it, and now...
You two.
I didn't see anything.
There's another replay.
I want to see that replay again.
Isn't it great to see a Japanese home run today? Wow, that's great. I'm so happy.
Mr. Furuyama and Makinon. Mr. Makinon.
Makinon? Yes, that's right.
Not "Makinon." Makinon.
Yes, that's right. You know... his name is "MC".
Like McDonald's? Like MacDonald? - Like MacDonald.
I'm alone.
I'm scared.
How's Black? Scary.
Oh, no, no, no...
We made it!
We made the finals.
Who's going to be in the baseball team?
We're in it now, Shiori, Yuna and Yan... 5 members.Sure, there's us, Shiori, Yuna and Yann in the group now. 5 members, right?
Well, who else do you want in? I don't know.
Mayu used to play softball. I'd like that.
Mayu and Aya? Yes, that's right.
Aya's a motto fan.
Aya is the most likely to join, isn't she? Hey, Christy...
I like this girl named Chihiro.
She's collaborating with the Lions here in the west.
They're going to put out some merchandise, and they want me to go watch them play.
Okay, I'll go with you.
We went to a Japan game the other day, remember?
You know, we went to see the Japan game, or rather, the double dooboo scene.
Kuromi paid for the ticket.
I told him I'd pay for it, and he said, "No, thanks.
So I'll take advantage.
I'm sorry. I told him I'd take him to yakiniku.
I told her we'd go to a barbecue.
Hold it down for the last time.
I won't wait.
It's great that Kuromi's on the Western side.
It's great that he's on the West side today.
He likes all the teams.
Yes, it is.
I'm going to buy a western eniform today, and spend the day alone as a western fan.
I'm so glad. I feel like I'm making new friends.I'm so glad I made a friend.
I became a friend!
We're friends now.
Oh, no, I'm out... he's gone.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no!
Oh, shit.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's okay, I haven't gone yet.
Three.
Yay!
That's good.
One more to go.
And here's Yamaguchi...
That's tough... go for it.
I just typed that.
I wish you'd stop.
Oh, no...
I won! I won!
I won!
Watch out!
Oh no...
I won!
Oh, thank goodness!Oh, thank God.
Thank God the sun is up.
The day is over.
I want to send this to Mass.
We won!
I'm so happy!
We can walk around the field after this.
I'm off to the field.
I'm off!
Look at all the people.
Wow!
Meow!
Meow, meow, meow!
So, here we are...
I've landed on the ground!
I'm so happy!
I'm stepping on the turf!
It's amazing, isn't it?
How was your day?
Well, first of all, I'm glad I got to see what the West has to offer.
Oh, that's great.
I've always loved the 12 teams.
I used to watch all of them.
I think I'm leaning a little bit toward the West again.I think I'm leaning a little toward the West again.
Oh, really?
I'm happy.
I'd love to go see the Western Lions.
We're like old friends today.
I got to see a baseball game.
I want to go to more games.
I want to go.
I felt like it was a private game, so I was able to relax and have fun.
That's what made me happy.
I was happy.
Oh, my God!
On September 1st, I'm going to throw out the first pitch for the Western Lions.
I'm going to throw out the first pitch!
Wow!
Thank you so much!
I've been practicing today.
I want to throw so hard that everyone will say "Hey!
I'll do my best.
Let's hope for a good drive.
You can count on me.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Subscribe and like our channel.Subscribe and like our channel
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye.